THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
The Capital Jury Project Records1941-20111990-2011
nam_apap196
The Capital Jury Project (CJP) was started in 1991 under the direction of principal investigation, William J. Bowers. The project was funded by an NSF grant to conduct surveys of juror who participated in capital trials. There are three phases to the project.
Bowers, William J.
81.8
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
Acquisition Information
All items in the Capital Jury Project Records were acquired by the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, through multiple donations from 2004-2015.
Biographical History
The Capital Jury Project was initiated in 1991 by a consortium of university-based researchers with support from the National Science Foundation. The Project is administered nationally by Dr. William Bowers, Principal Research Scientist, Northeastern University. The findings of the CJP are based on 3 to 4 hour, in-depth, interviews with persons who have served as jurors in capital trials. Phase I of the Project has completed over 1,200 interviews from jurors in 353 capital trials in 14 states. These interviews chronicled the jurors' experiences and decision-making over the course of the trial, identify points at which various influences come into play, and reveal the ways in which jurors reach their final sentencing decision. The project continued with the Capital Jury Project II (CJP2), a program of research on the decision-making of capital jurors.
The second phase, CJP2 ran from 2001 to roughly 2005 when the third phase of the project started. The second phase was housed at the University at Albany's School of Criminal Justice'sCapital Punishment Research Initiative, part of the Hindelang Criminal Justice Research Center. The main tenants of the research project were to (1) to build and maintain a national archive for historical documents and data on the death penalty; (2) to plan and conduct basic and policy related research on capital punishment; and (3) to encourage scholarship, conduct graduate and undergraduate training, and disseminate scientifically grounded knowledge about the ultimate penal sanction.
Principal Investigatorof the CJP is William J. Bowers (Ph.D., Columbia University, 1966). He was Principal Research Scientist in the School of Criminal Justice, University at Albany, formerly at Northeastern University. For his research on capital punishment, in 2000 Dr. Bowers received the American Society of Criminology's August Vollmer Award for outstanding contributions in applied criminology. Michael E. Antonio (Ph.D., Northeastern University, 2003) coordinated data management for the phase of the CJP on the role race plays in capital sentencing. Susan Ehrhard-Dietzel and Christopher E. Kelly (recent doctoral recipients at the University at Albany and Temple University, respectively) have assisted with the coordination and data management on the phase of the CJP concerned with jurors' receptivity to mitigation in capital sentencing.
Scope and Content Information
The Capital Jury records document the phases of the Capital Jury Research project. The collection contains materials ranging from 1979 to 2011 the bulk of the material is from 1991 to 2011. The collection is divided into parts that represent the life cycle of the whole project. The three phases, Capital Jury Project I, Capital Jury Project II, and Capital Jury Project III, which is still ongoing are comprised on materials that interviews used while conducting in person and phone interviews of former capital jury members. Also represented in the collection are publications and research from the findings of the interviews as well as research on the Death Penalty in the United States. The bulk of the collection focuses on the first phase of the Capital Jury Project which includes the interviews and audio cassettes of the interviews.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series: Series 1: CJP Phase I Subseries 1: State Interview Summaries Subseries 2: Administrative Subseries 3: Audiotapes of Juror Interviews Series 2: CJP Phase II Administrative Materials Series 3: CJP Phase III Subseries 1: State Interview Summaries Subseries 2: Administrative Subseries 3: Discs of Juror Interviews Series 4: William J. Bowers Subseries 1: Correspondence Subseries 2: Clemency Work Subseries 3: Scholarship and Teaching Series 5: Death Penalty Research Series 6: Publications Series 7: Subject Files Series 8: Death Penalty News Clippings
Access
Access to this record group is restricted. Researchers requesting access to records of the Capital Jury Project must adhere to the following conditions: 1) Researchers shall complete a Restricted Records Access Request form supplied by the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives and adequately describe the nature and purpose of their research; 2) Requests to photocopy or otherwise reproduce restricted records are prohibited; 3) Researchers may not publish or otherwise disclose any personally identifiable information from the materials in this collection; 4)Researchers may list the Sex, State, and Race of a juror when necessary and nothing else.
Subject and Genre Headings
Death Penalty; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Bowers, William J.; Acker, James R., 1951-; Baldus, David C.; Vandiver, Margaret; Antonio, Michael D.; Kelly, Christopher; Capital Jury Project; Abolition movement--United States; Capital punishment--Moral and ethical aspects; Capital punishment--United States; Death penalty; Correspondence; Criminal court records; Newsletters; Newspaper clippings; Papers; Official reports; Questionnaires; Syllabi
Container List
- CJP Phase I, 1990-2004; 1; 30.4
  Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  Arranged Alphabetically.
  Phase I of the Project has completed over 1,200 interviews from jurors in 353 capital trials in 14 states. These interviews chronicled the jurors' experiences and decision-making over the course of the trial, identify points at which various influences come into play, and reveal the ways in which jurors reach their final sentencing decision.
  - State Interview Summaries, 1991-2004; 1.1; 29.4
    This series is arranged alphabetically by state and juror number.
    This series includes the juror interview instruments from the first phase of the Capital Jury Project. It is arranged by state and then juror number. All of the interviews are restricted and cannot be reproduced.
    - Al 1801 Ephraim*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Al 1805 Madison*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Al 1806 Madison*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Al 1807 Madison*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Al 1809 Coral*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Al 1810 Coral*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Al 1811 Coral*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Al 1812 Coral*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Al 1813 Coral*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Al 1814 Coral*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - Al 1815 Mcnair*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Al 1819 Mcnair*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - al 1819 Gentry*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Al 1820 Gentry*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Al 1821 Gentry *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Al 1823 Scott*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Al 1824 Scott*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Al 1825 Scott*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Al 1827 Walker*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Al 1828 Walker*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Al 1829 Walker *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - AL 1830 Walker*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Al 1831 Walker*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Al 1832 Knotts*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Al 1833 Knotts*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Al 1834 Knotts*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Al 1836 Carr*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Al 1837 Carr*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Al 1838 Carr*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Al 1839 Carr*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Al 1840 Duncan *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Al 1841 Duncan *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Al 1842 Duncan*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Al 1843 Youngblood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Al 1844 Youngblood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Al 1845 Youngblood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Al 1846 Youngblood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Al 1847 Youngblood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Al 1848 Russaw*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Al 1849 Russaw*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Al 1852 Merriweather*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Al 1853 Merriweather*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Al 18534 Merriweather*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Al 1856 Flowers*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Al 1857 Flowers*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Al 1858 Flowers*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Al 1859 Flowers*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Al 1860 Flowers*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Al 1861 Dukes*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Al 1862 Dukes*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Al 1865 Smith J. *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Al 1866 Smith J.*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Al 1869 Hood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Al 1870 Hood *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Al 1871 Hood*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Al 1873 Hoff *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Al 1877 Nix*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Al 1878 Nix *RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Al 1881 Sockwell*RESTRICTED*, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - CA 0001 Umfress*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - CA 0002 Umfress*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - CA 0003 Umfress*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - CA 0004 Umfress*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - CA 0005 Yeoman*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - CA 0006 Yeoman*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - CA 0007 Yeoman*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - CA 0008 Yeoman*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - CA 0009 Majors*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - CA 0010 Majors*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - CA 0011 Majors*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - CA 0012 Majors*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - CA 1951 Majors *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - CA 1952 Majors *RESTRICTED*, 1995 August (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - CA 0013 Stewart *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - CA 0014 Stewart*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - CA 0015 Stewart *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - CA 0016 Stewart*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - CA 0018 Young*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - CA 0019 Young *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - CA 0025 Hines *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - CA 0026 Hines *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - CA 0027 Hines *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - CA 0028 Hines *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - CA 0030 Hines *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - CA 0030 Hines *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - CA 0021 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - CA 0022 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - CA 0023 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - CA 0024 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - CA 0031 Hawk *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - CA 0032 Hawk *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - CA 0033 Hawk *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - CA 0034 Hawk *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - CA 0150 Hawk *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - CA 0039 Cattera *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - CA 0040 Cattera *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - CA 0041 Cattera *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - CA 0042 Cattera *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - CA 0043 Arias *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - CA 0044 Arias *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - CA 0045 Arias *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - CA 0046 Arias *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - CA 0047 Arias*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - CA 0048 Stanley*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - CA 0049 Stanley *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - CA 0050 Stanley *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - CA 0052 Alvarez *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - CA 0054 Alvarez *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - CA 0053 Alvarez *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - CA 0055 Alvarez *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - CA 0056 Pacheco*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July 8 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - CA 0057 Pacheco *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - CA 0058 Pacheco *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - CA 0059 Pacheco *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - CA 0060 Pacheco *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - CA 0061 Jackson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - CA 0062 Jackson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - CA 0063 Jackson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - CA 0064 Jackson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - CA 0065 Covington *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - CA 0066 Covington *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CA 0067 Covington *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - CA 0068 Covington *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - CA 0069 Covington *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - CA 0070 Covington *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - CA 0071 Mussel White *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - CA 0072 Mussel White *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - CA 0073 Mussel White *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - CA 0074 Mussel White *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - CA 0075 Wash *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - CA 0076 Wash *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - CA 0077 Wash *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - CA 0078 Wash *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - CA 0148 Wash *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - CA Williams *RESTRICTED*, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - CA Schmeck *RESTRICTED*, 2001 July (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - CA 0079 Schmeck *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July 8 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - CA 0080 Schmeck*RESTRICTED*, 1992 July 8 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - CA 0083 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - CA 0084 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - CA 0085 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - CA 0086 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - CA 0087 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - CA 0088 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - CA 0089 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - CA 0090 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - CA 0091 Staedel *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - CA 0092 Staedel *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - CA 0093 Staedel *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - CA 0094 Staedel *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - CA 0095 Allen *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - CA 0096 allen *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - CA 0097 Allen *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - CA 0099 Rector *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - CA 0100 Rector *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - CA 0101 Rector *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - CA 0102 Rector *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - CA 0103 Carter *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - CA 0104 Carter *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - CA 0105 Carter *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - CA 0107 Osband *RESTRICTED*, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - CA 0108 Osband *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - CA 0111 Celestine *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - CA 0112 Celestine *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - CA 0113 Celestine *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - CA 0114 Celestine *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - CA 0115 Celestine *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - CA 0118 White *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - CA 0119 white *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - CA 0120 White *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - CA 0121 Robinson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - CA 0122 Robinson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - CA 0123 Robinson *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July 8 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - CA 0125 Goodfellow *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - CA 0126 Goodfellow *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - CA 0127 Goodfellow *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - CA 0128 Goodfellow *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - CA 0129 Goodfellow *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - CA 0130 Hawkins *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - CA 0131 Hawkins *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - CA 0132 Hawkins *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - CA 0133 Hawkins *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - CA 0134 Hawkins *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CA 0135 Hawkins *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - CA 0136 Welch *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - CA 0137 Welch *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - CA 0138 Welch *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - CA 0140 Welch *RESTRICTED*, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - CA 0141 Johnson*RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - CA 0142 Johnson *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - CA 0144 Barbosa *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - CA 0145 Barbosa*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - CA 0149 Mussel White*RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - CA 1953 Salcido *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - CA 1954 Salcido *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - CA 1955 Salcido *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - CA 1956 Salcido *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - CA 1957 Salcido *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - CA 1958 Stahl *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - CA 1959 Stahl *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - CA 1960 Stahl *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - CA 1962 Spears *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - CA 1963 Spears *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - CA 1964 Spears *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - CA 1965 Spears *RESTRICTED*, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - FL 0151 Hodges *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - FL 0152 Hodges *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - FL 0153 Hodges *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - FL 0154 Hodges *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - FL 0155 Myers *RESTRICTED*, 1991 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - FL 0156 Myers *RESTRICTED*, 1991 December (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - FL 0157 Myers *RESTRICTED*, 1991 December (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - FL 0158 Myers *RESTRICTED*, 1991 December (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - FL 0159 White *RESTRICTED*, 1991 December (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - FL 0160 White *RESTRICTED*, 1991 December (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - FL 0161 White *RESTRICTED*, 1998 April (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - FL 0162 White *RESTRICTED*, 1998 April (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - FL 0167 Valentine *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - FL 0168 Valentine*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - FL 0169 Valentine *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - FL 0170 Valentine *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - FL 0171 Gore *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - FL 0172 Gore *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - FL 0173 Gore *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - FL 0174 Gore *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - FL 0175 Ponticelli *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - FL 0176 Ponticelli *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - FL 0177 Ponticelli *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - FL 0178 Ponticelli *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - FL 0183 Pilgrim *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - FL 0184 Pilgrim *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - FL 0185 Pilgrim *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - FL 0186 Pilgrim *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - FL 0187 Smith*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - FL 0188 Smith*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - FL 0189 Smith*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - FL 0190 Smith*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - FL 0191 Thompson *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - FL 0192 Thompson*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - FL 0193 Thompson*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - FL 0194 Thompson *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - FL 0195 Jenkins *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - FL 0196 Jenkins*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Fl 0197 Jenkins *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - FL 0198 Jenkins *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - FL 0199 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - FL 0200 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - FL 0203 Santos *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - FL 0204 Santos *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - FL 0205 Santos *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - FL 0206 Santos *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fl 0207 Hoefert *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - FL 0208 Hoefert *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - FL 0209 Hoefert *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - FL 0210 Hoefert *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - FL 0211 Mitchell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - FL 0212 Mitchell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - FL 0213 Mitchell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - FL 0215 Maulden *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - FL 0216 Maulden *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - FL 2017 Maulden *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - FL 2018 Maulden *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - FL 0219 Randolph *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - FL 0220 Randolph *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - FL 0221 Randolph *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Fl 0222 Randolph *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - FL 0223 Burney *RESTRICTED*, 1992 August (Box 7, Folder 23)